A Finding Aid to the Lee Nordness business records and papers, circa 1931-1992 (bulk 1954-1984), in the Archives of American Art AAA.nordlee
Archives of American Art
- Nordness Gallery, Inc. and Lee Nordness Galleries Art Advisory Section, Inc., bulk 1958-1982; circa 1938-1992; Series 1; 67.8 Linear feet Boxes 1-67, 117-119
  - Project Files, 1952-1990; 1.3
    Abbreviations used for projects include: Circle of Arts/Objects, "A/O"; Cooper-Hewitt, National Museum of Design, "NMD"; and, Metromedia, Inc. (Mr. X) Art Collection, "X."
    The series is arranged as 8 subseries.
    - Art:USA: The Johnson Collection of Contemporary American Painting, 1959-1967; 1.3.1
      Folders are arranged alphabetically by folder title.
      The bulk of the materials found here are clippings about the traveling exhibition Art:USA:NOW and the exhibition book for Art:USA: The Johnson Collection of Contemporary American Painting. Also found is correspondence, photographs of artists, paid bill receipts, and other types of business records. Notably missing are records related to the development of the collection.
      - Billed to "Art:USA:NOW", 1962-1964 (Box 19, Folder 5)
      - Book and Postcard Sales, 1962-1965 (Box 19, Folder 6-7)
      - Book Orders and Dispositions, 1962-1964 (Box 19, Folder 8)
      - Brochures, 1960s (Box 19, Folder 9)
      - C.J. Bucher Ltd. Lucerne Book, 1961-1965 (Box 19, Folder 10-13)
      - Catalog Dummy, circa 1961-1967 (Box 19, Folder 14)
      - Clippings, 1962-1963 (Box 19, Folder 15)
        Oversized material housed in Box 118, Folder 2
      - Clippings (Box 19)
        - European Cities, 1962-1964 (Box 19, Folder 16)
        - Greece, 1963 (Box 19, Folder 17)
        - Paris, 1964 (Box 19, Folder 18)
        - Toronto and Mexico, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 19)
        - U.S. Cities, 1965-1967 (Box 19, Folder 20)
      - Clippings, U.S. Cities, 1964-1967 (Box 20, Folder 1-3)
      - Clippings, Various Cities, 1964-1967 (Box 20, Folder 4)
      - Exhibition Postcards, 1963 (Box 20, Folder 5)
      - Paid Bills, 1961-1963 (Box 20, Folder 6-7)
      - Photographs, circa 1964 (Box 20, Folder 8)
      - Photographs of "Art:USA:NOW" Artists, 1960s (Box 20, Folder 9-10)
        Oversized material housed in Box 118, Folder 3
      - Photographs, Opening in Berlin, 1960s (Box 20, Folder 11)
      - Postcards, 1963-1965 (Box 20, Folder 12)
      - Postcards, E.M. Priebat, 1962-1964 (Box 20, Folder 13)
      - Public Relations, Paris, 1964 (Box 20, Folder 14)
      - Scrapbook Pages, 1959-1964 (Box 20, Folder 15-16)
      - Travel Expenses, 1962 (Box 20, Folder 17)
      - Oversized Clippings, 1962 (Box 118, Folder 2)
        Oversized material from Box 19, Folder 15
      - Oversized Photographs of "Art:USA:NOW" Artists, 1960s (Box 118, Folder 3)
        Oversized material from Box 20, Folder 9
    - Objects:USA: Johnson Contemporary Crafts Art Collection, 1968-1981; 1.3.2
      Found are records documenting the development and final disposition of the Objects: USA collection and the accompanying traveling exhibition. Materials include appraisal records, correspondence, index cards for artists, tour records, and voluminous newspaper clippings. Artist's files related to Objects: USA are found in subseries 1.2.
      - Appraisal Forms, circa 1977 (Box 20, Folder 18)
      - Appraisal Forms Completed and Sent to Racine, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 19)
      - Appraisal Forms Sent to Appraisers, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 20)
      - Appraisals, 1977-1981 (Box 20, Folder 21)
      - Appraisals (Box 20)
        - Artist Replacements, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 22)
        - Museum Rejections, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 23)
        - Price Inventory, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 24)
      - Appraisals and Dispositions, 1977-1981 (Box 20, Folder 25)
      - Appraisals for Restorations, 1976-1977 (Box 20, Folder 26)
      - Artist's Bills of Sales, 1968-1970 (Box 20, Folder 27)
      - Artist's Bills of Sales, 1968-1969 (Box 21, Folder 1)
      - Book (Box 21)
        - Macmillan Company, 1968-1969 (Box 21, Folder 2)
        - Original Text, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 3)
        - Text, circa 1968-1969 (Box 21, Folder 4)
        - Text Changes, 1968-1969 (Box 21, Folder 5-6)
      - Brochures, circa 1960s (Box 21, Folder 7)
      - Cirker's Hayes Storage Warehouse, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 8)
      - Correspondence, 1977 June-September (Box 21, Folder 9-11)
      - Correspondence Regarding Appraisals, 1975; 1977 (Box 21, Folder 12-13)
      - Correspondence, These Letters are Finish, 1977-1979 (Box 21, Folder 14)
      - European Tour, circa 1972 (Box 21, Folder 15)
      - Filled-in Appraisals From Artists and Other Appraisers - To Racine, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 16-17)
      - Filmstrip Script, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 18)
      - Form Letters, 1977; circa 1968-1970 (Box 21, Folder 19-21)
      - Friedlander, Steve, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 22)
      - Gifts, The Museum of Contemporary Crafts, 1976-1978 (Box 21, Folder 23-24)
      - Guest Books, 1973-1974 (Box 21, Folder 25)
        Oversized material housed in Box 118, Folder 4
      - Index Cards, Artists (3 shoeboxes), circa 1968-1977 (Box 22, Folder 1-3)
      - Inventories, New York and Museum of Contemporary Crafts, 1974-1979 (Box 23, Folder 1)
      - The Museum of Contemporary Crafts, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 2)
      - Not Being Used in Collection, circa 1970s (Box 23, Folder 3)
      - Notes for Objects:USA, circa 1969 (Box 23, Folder 4)
      - Permissions to Reproduce, 1975-1976 (Box 23, Folder 5)
      - Photographic Materials, late 1960s-1975 (Box 23, Folder 6-7)
      - Photographs, 1970s (Box 23, Folder 8)
      - Press Clippings, 1968-1971 (Box 23, Folder 9-24)
      - Press Clippings Scrapbook, 1968-1969 (Box 23, Folder 25)
      - Press Releases and Public Relations, circa 1968-1970 (Box 23, Folder 26)
      - Price List, circa 1969 (Box 23, Folder 27)
      - Prospectus, 1968 (Box 23, Folder 28)
      - Show Changes, 1969-1970s (Box 24, Folder 1)
      - Slides Requested (Form F or Equivalent), 1968-1969 (Box 24, Folder 2)
      - Tour [Museums and Galleries], 1968-1972 (Box 24, Folder 3-28)
      - Tour Requests From Museums and Galleries, 1968-1973 (Box 24, Folder 29)
      - Tour Schedule, circa 1969 (Box 24, Folder 30)
      - Undelivered Mail to Artists, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 31)
      - Oversized Guest Books, 1973-1974 (Box 118, Folder 4)
        Oversized material from Box 20, Folder 25
    - Circle of Arts/Objects, 1963-1978; 1.3.3
      Includes correspondence, customer files, artist's files arranged by craft, and sales invoices for Circle of Arts/Objects direct mail and sales, and the accompanying travelling exhibition, Arts/Objects:USA. Artist's files related to Circle of Arts/Objects are found in subseries 1.2.
      - Adamiak, Adam, 1972 (Box 24, Folder 32)
      - African Art, circa 1972-1973 (Box 24, Folder 33)
      - American Crafts Council, 1970-1973 (Box 24, Folder 34)
      - American Crafts Council, Outlook, 1970-1972 (Box 24, Folder 35)
      - American Folk Art, circa 1972-1973 (Box 24, Folder 36)
      - Artist's Biographies, circa 1968-1970s (Box 24, Folder 37-38)
      - "Arts/Objects:USA" Printed Materials Scrapbook, 1970s (Box 24, Folder 39)
      - Barnes Press, Inc., 1972-1973 (Box 24, Folder 40)
      - Bills, Unpaid, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 41)
      - Board Report (March 9, 1973) (Box 24, Folder 42)
      - Bookbinding, circa 1973 (Box 24, Folder 43)
      - Candles, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 44)
      - Case-Hoyt Printing, 1972 (Box 24, Folder 45)
      - Catalog, Arts/Objects:USA, 1970s (Box 24, Folder 46)
      - Ceramics, 1968-1976 (Box 24, Folder 47-48)
      - Ceramics (Box 24)
        - Adamson, Jimmy C., 1973-1974 (Box 24, Folder 49)
        - Baldwin, Douglas, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 50)
        - Bovard, Ana J., 1971-1973; 1967 (Box 24, Folder 51)
        - Burgess, Joseph, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 52)
        - Colson, Frank, circa 1973 (Box 24, Folder 53)
        - Cushing, Val, 1972 (Box 24, Folder 54)
        - Dudchenko, Boris and Nancy, 1972 (Box 24, Folder 55)
        - Eaker, 1967-1968 (Box 24, Folder 56)
        - Fenton, Sophia, 1972 (Box 24, Folder 57)
        - Fleming, Frank, circa 1975-1978 (Box 24, Folder 58)
        - Funk, Verne, 1971-1972 (Box 24, Folder 59)
        - Gernhardt, Henry, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 60)
        - Hara, Teruo, 1974-1975; 1968 (Box 24, Folder 61)
        - James, Esta, 1972 (Box 24, Folder 62)
        - Jones, Harrison, 1971-1972 (Box 24, Folder 63)
        - Kilnhaus Potters, 1973-1974 (Box 24, Folder 64)
        - Lyman, 1970-1972 (Box 24, Folder 65)
        - McCullum, Mike, 1970-1973 (Box 24, Folder 66)
        - Nagle, Ron, 1972 (Box 24, Folder 67)
        - Nicholas, Donna L., 1972 (Box 24, Folder 68)
        - Peterson, Dale, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 69)
        - Reed, Mike, 1968 (Box 24, Folder 70)
        - Rippe, Jim, 1973-1974 (Box 24, Folder 71)
      - Ceramics (Box 25)
        - Rosana, Evelyn, 1968 (Box 25, Folder 1)
        - Schecter, Jane, 1973 (Box 25, Folder 2)
        - Schneider, Richard D., 1970-1973 (Box 25, Folder 3)
        - Silverman, David, 1972-1973 (Box 25, Folder 4)
        - Tell, David, 1971-1972 (Box 25, Folder 5)
        - Temple, Byron, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 6)
        - Tepper, Irving, 1973 (Box 25, Folder 7)
        - Vance, George W., 1971-1972 (Box 25, Folder 8)
        - Woodman, Betty, 1972-1973 (Box 25, Folder 9)
      - Check Stubs, 1974 (Box 25, Folder 10)
      - Check Stubs and Bank Deposit Book, circa 1972-1974 (Box 25, Folder 11)
      - Consignment Sheets, 1973 (Box 25, Folder 12)
      - Correspondence, 1972-1978 (Box 25, Folder 13-15)
      - Correspondence (Box 25)
        - Mail Order Responses, 1970s (Box 25, Folder 16)
        - Memograms, 1973 (Box 25, Folder 17)
        - Museums, 1972-1974 (Box 25, Folder 18)
        - Requests for Catalogs, 1972-1977 (Box 25, Folder 19)
      - Robert Crandall Associates, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 20)
      - Credit Cards, 1972-1975 (Box 25, Folder 21-23)
      - Craft Groups, 1970s (Box 25, Folder 24)
      - Craft Schools, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 25)
      - Customer Cards, circa 1973 (Box 25, Folder 26)
      - Customer Files, 1973-1975 (Box 25, Folder 27-32)
      - D & A Printing, 1972-1973 (Box 25, Folder 33)
      - Documents, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 34)
      - Enamels, 1969-1975 (Box 25, Folder 35)
      - Enamels (Box 25)
        - Balazs, Harold, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 36)
        - Hofstrom, Juanita, 1973 (Box 25, Folder 37)
        - James, Catherine, 1973 (Box 25, Folder 38)
        - Krevit, Rose, 1973-1974 (Box 25, Folder 39)
        - Whitcomb, Kay, 1973 (Box 25, Folder 40)
      - Eskimo Art, circa 1971-1973 (Box 25, Folder 41)
      - Fairs Announcements, 1972-1974 (Box 25, Folder 42)
      - Fiber, 1973-1976 (Box 25, Folder 43-44)
      - Fiber (Box 26)
        - Belfer, Nancy, 1972-1973 (Box 26, Folder 1)
        - Bittleman, Dolores D., 1973 (Box 26, Folder 2)
        - Burgess, Anna Kang, 1971-1973 (Box 26, Folder 3)
        - Colby, Sas, 1973 (Box 26, Folder 4)
        - Cusack, Margaret, 1973-1975 (Box 26, Folder 5)
        - Daeger, Polly, 1973 (Box 26, Folder 6)
        - Davis, Lenore, 1973 (Box 26, Folder 7)
        - Dobek, Ann Dushanko, 1973 (Box 26, Folder 8)
        - Eagerton, Mari, 1971-1973 (Box 26, Folder 9)
        - Fischer, Mildred, 1972-1973 (Box 26, Folder 10)
        - Friberg, Kristina, 1975 (Box 26, Folder 11)
        - Harrison, Charles, 1973-1974 (Box 26, Folder 12)
        - Klein, Jody, 1973 (Box 26, Folder 13)
        - Knorr, Jeanne Boardman, 1971-1973 (Box 26, Folder 14)
        - Kritzer, Rona, 1973 (Box 26, Folder 15)
        - Pague, Joan Michaels, 1973 (Box 26, Folder 16)
        - Proctor, Richard M. and Jennifer Lew, 1973 (Box 26, Folder 17)
        - Puryear, Marjorie D., 1973 (Box 26, Folder 18)
        - Sage, Priscilla, 1976-1977 (Box 26, Folder 19)
        - Sauer, Dick, 1972-1975 (Box 26, Folder 20)
        - Schira, Cynthia, 1973 (Box 26, Folder 21)
        - Schwartzott, Carol, 1973 (Box 26, Folder 22)
        - Smith, Carter, 1972-1973 (Box 26, Folder 23)
        - Uyemora, Ken J., 1971-1972 (Box 26, Folder 24)
        - Waddington, Linda, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 25)
        - Weaving, 1971-1975; 1965-1967 (Box 26, Folder 26)
      - First National City Bank, 1972-1975 (Box 26, Folder 27)
      - Form Letters, 1970s (Box 26, Folder 28)
      - General Offset Printing Co., circa 1972 (Box 26, Folder 29)
      - Glass, 1971-1975 (Box 26, Folder 30)
      - Glass (Box 26)
        - Dailey, Dan, 1971-1974 (Box 26, Folder 31)
        - Fenton, Dan, 1970-1974 (Box 26, Folder 32)
        - Higgins, Michael, 1972-1973 (Box 26, Folder 33)
        - Hyams, Harriet, 1973-1974 (Box 26, Folder 34)
        - Kilby, Ruth M., 1973 (Box 26, Folder 35)
        - Levin, Robert, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 36)
        - Ross, Ann, 1967-1968; 1971-1973 (Box 26, Folder 37)
        - Smith, Drew, 1975 (Box 26, Folder 38)
        - Solon, Suzanne, 1972-1973 (Box 26, Folder 39)
        - Sowers, Robert, 1973 (Box 26, Folder 40)
        - Strum, Dorothy, 1972-1974 (Box 26, Folder 41)
        - Tanner, James, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 42)
        - Walton, Hilda, 1970-1973 (Box 26, Folder 43)
        - Wilson, David J.C., 1975 (Box 26, Folder 44)
      - Glass Blowers, 1973-1975 (Box 26, Folder 45)
      - Ideas, 1969-1976 (Box 26, Folder 46)
      - Instapak, 1973 (Box 26, Folder 47)
      - Inventory Payments, 1972-1973 (Box 26, Folder 48)
      - Invoices, 1972-1973 (Box 26, Folder 49-50)
      - Jewelry, 1967-1975 (Box 27, Folder 1-2)
      - Jewelry (Box 27)
        - Arentzen, Glenda, 1972-1973 (Box 27, Folder 3)
        - Blyth, Bruce W., 1973 (Box 27, Folder 4)
        - Engle, Barbara, 1973 (Box 27, Folder 5)
        - Evans, Gerry, 1972-1973 (Box 27, Folder 6)
        - Morris, W. Kelley, 1973 (Box 27, Folder 7)
        - Pine, Alvin A., 1968; circa 1973 (Box 27, Folder 8)
        - Steen, Carol J., 1973 (Box 27, Folder 9)
        - Wreden, Peter, 1973 (Box 27, Folder 10)
      - Johnson, Samuel, 1973-1975 (Box 27, Folder 11)
      - S.C. Johnson & Son, Closing, 1973 (Box 27, Folder 12)
      - Johnson Wax (Box 27)
        - Bloomquist, Al, 1972-1975 (Box 27, Folder 13)
        - Jones, E.O. (Public Relations), 1973-1975 (Box 27, Folder 14)
        - Moll, Jack, 1972-1973 (Box 27, Folder 15)
        - Objects Available, 1973-1975 (Box 27, Folder 16)
      - Lackie, 1972-1973 (Box 27, Folder 17)
      - Leather, 1972-1974 (Box 27, Folder 18)
      - Legal Agreements, 1972 (Box 27, Folder 19)
      - Legal Correspondence, 1972-1973 (Box 27, Folder 20)
      - Mailing Lists, 1969-1975 (Box 27, Folder 21-23)
      - Mailing Lists and Requests for Catalogs, 1974-1975 (Box 27, Folder 24)
      - Metal, 1971-1974 (Box 27, Folder 25)
      - Metal (Box 27)
        - Daly, Steven, 1972-1973 (Box 27, Folder 26)
        - Hirsh, Annette, 1970-1973 (Box 27, Folder 27)
        - Mawdsley, Richard, 1974-1975 (Box 27, Folder 28)
        - Michaels, Glen, 1973 (Box 27, Folder 29)
        - Nelson, Mary Stephens, 1973 (Box 27, Folder 30)
        - Rutherford, William, 1973-1975 (Box 27, Folder 31)
      - Museum Shops, 1970s (Box 27, Folder 32)
      - Native American Art, 1963-1973 (Box 27, Folder 33)
      - New Artists, 1972-1973 (Box 27, Folder 34)
      - New Artists Whose Slides We Do Not Have, 1972-1973 (Box 27, Folder 35)
      - Paper, 1973-1974 (Box 27, Folder 36)
      - Petty Cash, 1973 (Box 27, Folder 37)
      - Plastic, 1970-1973 (Box 27, Folder 38)
      - Plastic, Ralph and Sylvia Massey, 1973 (Box 27, Folder 39)
      - Post Office Account, 1973 (Box 27, Folder 40)
      - Prospectus, 1972 (Box 27, Folder 41)
      - Purchasing Procedures, 1973 (Box 27, Folder 42)
      - Rejected Artists, 1972-1973 (Box 27, Folder 43)
      - Sales Catalogs, 1975-1976 (Box 27, Folder 44)
      - Sales Invoices, 1972-1973 (Box 27, Folder 45)
      - Sanders Printing, 1972-1973 (Box 28, Folder 1)
      - Scheduled Mailings, Inc., 1972-1973 (Box 28, Folder 2)
      - Seminars, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 3)
      - Signed Test Mailing Forms, 1972 (Box 28, Folder 4)
      - Statistics, 1970s (Box 28, Folder 5-6)
      - Statistics (Box 28)
        - Cost Breakdown for First Catalog, 1970s (Box 28, Folder 7)
        - Evaluation of Arts/Objects:USA, 1973 (Box 28, Folder 8)
        - Mailing List Breakdown, 1970s (Box 28, Folder 9)
        - Sales Reports, 1973 (Box 28, Folder 10)
        - Statistics #1, circa 1972 (Box 28, Folder 11)
      - Taxes, 1973 (Box 28, Folder 12)
      - TGC, 1972 (Box 28, Folder 13)
      - Walter Weintz and Co., 1972-1973 (Box 28, Folder 14-15)
      - Wholesale, 1971-1976 (Box 28, Folder 16)
      - Wood, 1972-1976 (Box 28, Folder 17)
      - Wood (Box 28)
        - Blunk, J.R., 1971-1973 (Box 28, Folder 18)
        - Hayes, Reverand, 1973 (Box 28, Folder 19)
        - Kapel, John, 1973 (Box 28, Folder 20)
        - Maloof, Sam, 1972 (Box 28, Folder 21)
        - Miller, Birdie, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 22)
        - Remington, J.D., circa 1973 (Box 28, Folder 23)
        - Risley, John, 1973 (Box 28, Folder 24)
        - Valenza, Daniel, 1971-1972 (Box 28, Folder 25)
        - Walker, I.M., 1974-1975 (Box 28, Folder 26)
        - Young, Roy, 1975-1976 (Box 28, Folder 27)
      - Wood Furniture, 1973-1974 (Box 28, Folder 28)
    - Cooper-Hewitt, National Museum of Design, 1968-1981; 1.3.4
      Found are records regarding planning the opening exhibition, MANtransFORMS, the organization of a craft fair, and other business proposals for the museum. Materials include correspondence and business records. Additional documents related to the craft fair are found in subseries 3.1.
      - Ardalan + Schlamminger, circa 1970s (Box 28, Folder 29)
      - Artist Possibilities, 1980 (Box 28, Folder 30)
      - Artist's Contact Information, circa 1980 (Box 28, Folder 31)
      - Artists Under Consideration (Museum), circa 1979-1980 (Box 28, Folder 32)
      - Brochure Text, "MANtransFORMS", circa 1976 (Box 28, Folder 33)
      - China, 1974-1976 (Box 28, Folder 34)
      - China, The Gorham Company - Waylande Gregory, 1974 (Box 28, Folder 35)
      - China, Tiles, circa 1974-1976 (Box 28, Folder 36)
      - Correspondence, 1973-1976 (Box 28, Folder 37)
      - Correspondence To Be Filed, 1976-1977 (Box 28, Folder 38)
      - Craft Fair (Box 28)
        - Artist Recommendations, 1980-1981 (Box 28, Folder 39)
        - Booth Sales, 1981 (Box 28, Folder 40)
        - Correspondence, 1980 (Box 28, Folder 41)
        - Form Letters, May Show, 1981 (Box 28, Folder 42)
        - Invited, 1981 (Box 28, Folder 43)
        - Invitees, Pre-Selected for September Show, circa 1980 (Box 28, Folder 44)
        - Map and Booths, 1980 (Box 28, Folder 45)
        - Marnia Wormus, 1980 (Box 28, Folder 46)
        - Paid Artists From September Show, circa 1980 (Box 28, Folder 47)
        - Press Release, September, 1980 (Box 28, Folder 48)
      - Design, Miscellaneous, 1972-1975 (Box 28, Folder 49)
      - Design Contract, S.C. Johnson & Son and Smithsonian, 1972-1976 (Box 28, Folder 50)
      - Design Project Literature, 1970s (Box 28, Folder 51)
      - Design Project Literature, 1970s (Box 29, Folder 1)
      - Eames, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 2)
      - Fabric, 1975; 1980 (Box 29, Folder 3)
      - Fabric (Box 29)
        - Dobkin, John, 1976-1978 (Box 29, Folder 4)
        - Needlepoint, circa 1975-1977 (Box 29, Folder 5)
        - Savant, 1977-1978 (Box 29, Folder 6)
        - Stevens, J.P., 1976-1977 (Box 29, Folder 7)
        - Ticking-Golding, 1978 (Box 29, Folder 8)
        - Waverly, circa 1975-1977 (Box 29, Folder 9)
      - Film, LN [Lee Nordness], 1970s (Box 29, Folder 10)
      - Film, "MANtransFORMS", 1976-1977 (Box 29, Folder 11)
      - Film, Miscellaneous, 1976-1977 (Box 29, Folder 12)
      - Fuller, Buckminster, 1975-1977 (Box 29, Folder 13)
      - Fuller, Buckminster, Jan Bochenck, 1977 (Box 29, Folder 14)
      - Fuller, Buckminster, Johnson Contract, 1976 (Box 29, Folder 15)
      - Guidelines, 1974 (Box 29, Folder 16)
      - Hollein, Hans, 1973-1977; 1968 (Box 29, Folder 17)
      - Hollein, Hans and Martin, 1975-1977 (Box 29, Folder 18)
      - Homer, Winslow and Ostrow, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 19)
      - Inventory, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 20)
      - Johnson, Samuel, circa 1974-1975 (Box 29, Folder 21)
      - MANtransFORMS (Catalog), 1976 (Box 29, Folder 22)
      - "MANtransFORMS" Press Kit, 1976-1977 (Box 29, Folder 23)
      - Museum Store, 1972-1977 (Box 29, Folder 24)
      - New York Stationary Show, circa 1975 (Box 29, Folder 25)
      - Nordness, Lee, Bills, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 26)
      - Nordness, Lee, Contract, 1972-1973 (Box 29, Folder 27)
      - Opening Exhibition Background Information on Conceptualizer and Contributers, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 28)
      - Opening Exhibition Concept, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 29)
        Oversized material housed in Box 118, Folder 5
      - Paper, 1977 (Box 29, Folder 30)
      - Paper (Box 29)
        - American Greetings Co., 1976 (Box 29, Folder 31)
        - American Heritage, 1976-1977 (Box 29, Folder 32)
        - Hallmark Cards, 1975-1976 (Box 29, Folder 33)
        - B. Shackman & Co., 1976 (Box 29, Folder 34)
      - Press, 1976 (Box 29, Folder 35)
      - Product Promotion, 1976-1977 (Box 29, Folder 36)
      - Product Promotion Contract, 1975-1979 (Box 29, Folder 37)
      - Prospectus to Johnson, 1971 (Box 29, Folder 38)
      - Pulos, Arthur, 1973 (Box 29, Folder 39)
      - Scenario, Etc., 1981; 1970s (Box 29, Folder 40)
      - Slide Inventory, 1970s (Box 29, Folder 41)
      - Struver, Kurt, 1980 (Box 29, Folder 42)
      - Taylor, Lisa, 1971-1977 (Box 29, Folder 43)
      - Tour Requests, 1976-1977 (Box 29, Folder 44)
      - Wallpaper, 1972-1975 (Box 29, Folder 45)
      - Wallpaper (Box 29)
        - Brunschwig & Fils, Inc., circa 1980 (Box 29, Folder 46)
        - Colin & Aikman, 1978-1979 (Box 29, Folder 47)
        - Reed, 1979-1980 (Box 29, Folder 48)
        - Twigs, 1976 (Box 29, Folder 49)
      - Windowshades, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 50)
      - Wingspread Conference, 1970s (Box 29, Folder 51)
      - Oversized, Opening Exhibition Concept, 1975 (Box 118, Folder 5)
        Oversized material from Box 29, Folder 29
    - Council House Collection, 1968-1984; 1952; 1.3.5
      This sub-subseries documents the development of the international art collection for the Council House, a lodging building at the Johnson Wax Wind Project Conference Center. Materials include business correspondence; country files containing correspondence and biographies of artists; and files regarding the publication of a catalog.
      - Acquisitions, 1978-1979 (Box 29, Folder 52)
      - Art Spaces, 1978 (Box 29, Folder 53)
      - Artists, Possible, 1977 (Box 29, Folder 54)
      - Artwork Index Cards, circa 1978-1979 (Box 29, Folder 55)
      - Artwork Index Cards, circa 1978-1979 (Box 30, Folder 1)
      - Book (Box 30)
        - I-XV, circa 1978-1980 (Box 30, Folder 2-17)
        - Catlines, 1979-1980 (Box 30, Folder 18)
        - Changes, 1980-1981 (Box 30, Folder 19)
        - Contract, 1979-1980 (Box 30, Folder 20)
        - Correspondence, 1980 (Box 30, Folder 21)
        - Hamilton, Phil, 1979-1980 (Box 30, Folder 22)
        - Held, Jeff, 1979-1980 (Box 30, Folder 23)
        - Ioconetti, Mary, 1980 (Box 30, Folder 24)
        - Jones, Jim, 1980 (Box 30, Folder 25)
        - Perimeter Press Billings, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 26)
        - Perimeter Press Correspondence, 1979-1980 (Box 30, Folder 27)
        - Philosophy, 1979-1980 (Box 30, Folder 28)
        - Printing, 1980-1981 (Box 30, Folder 29)
        - Screen, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 30)
        - Screen Foldout, circa 1978-1980 (Box 30, Folder 31)
        - Seiser, Neal, 1978 (Box 30, Folder 32)
        - Unfiled - Mainly Correspondence With Four Designers, 1980 (Box 30, Folder 33)
      - Catalog, Preliminary, circa 1980 (Box 30, Folder 34-35)